# EVAN JOHNSON

### SKILLS

#### General

Detail-oriented, time management, creative

#### **Ecommerce**

Google analytics, Shopify, Klaviyo

#### Web development

HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Javascript, jQuery, SQL, C++, Photoshop

# EXPERIENCE

Ecommerce manager | Country Bargain Bin August 2019 – Present

Web design
Content creation
Inventory management
SEO
Email marketing
Social media marketing

## Optician | SIGHT | May 2019 - Present

Office administration, multi-task management, sales

Optician | Canton South Eyecare February 2017- April 2019

Office administration, multi-task management, sales

## SUMMARY

Optician with 3+ years of administrative and sales experience and 1 year of ecommerce/web development experience looking to build a career in a company that invests in its employees and cultivates a productive and healthy atmosphere.





Johnsonec16 @gmail.com

740-424-1162



Evan Johnson LinkedIn

# EDUCATION

Bachelor's in Psychology April 2016 Mount Vernon Nazarene University